Guide to the Graduate School of Arts and Sciences, Yale University, Student Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
- Grade rosters and student records, 1920-2003; Bulk 1990-2003; Accession 2016-A-065
  - Graduate School of Arts and Sciences (GSAS) Grade Rosters
    - Religious Studies, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 22-23)
    - Renaissance Studies, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 24-25)
    - Russian and East European Studies, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 26-27)
    - Slavic Languages Literatures, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 28-29)
    - Sociology, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 30-31)
    - Spanish and Portuguese, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 32-33)
    - Statistics, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 34-35)
    - Theatre Studies, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 36-37)
    - Women's, Gender, and Sexuality Studies, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 38-39)
    - Professional Schools
      - Divinity School, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 40-41)
      - Law School, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 42-43)
      - Management, School of, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 44-45)
      - Medical School, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 46-47)
      - Music, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 48-49)
    - Teacher Prep, 1997-1998 (Box 11, Folder 50-51)
    - African American Studies, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 52-53)
    - African Studies, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 54-55)
    - American Studies, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 56-57)
    - Anthropology, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 58-59)
    - Archaeology, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 60-61)
    - Astronomy, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 62-63)
    - Biology, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 64-65)
    - Cell Biology, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 66-67)
    - Cellular Molecular Physiology, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 68-69)
    - Chemistry, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 70-71)
    - Classics, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 72-73)
    - Comparative Literature, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 74-75)
    - Computer Science, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 76-77)
    - East Asian Languages Literatures, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 78-79)
    - East Asian Studies, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 80-81)
    - Ecology Evolutionary Biology, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 82-83)
    - Economics, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 84-85)
    - Engineering Applied Science, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 86-87)
    - English, 1998-1999 (Box 11, Folder 88-89)
    - Epidemiology Public Health, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 1-2)
    - Forestry and Environmental Studies, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 3-4)
    - French, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 5-6)
    - Genetics, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 7-8)
    - Geology Geophysics, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 9-10)
    - Germanic Languages Literatures, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 11-12)
    - History, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 13-14)
    - History of Art, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 15-16)
    - History of Science, History of Medicine, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 17-18)
    - Immunobiology, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 19-20)
    - International Relations, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - Italian Language Literature, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 22-23)
    - Linguistics, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 24-25)
    - Literature, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Management, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 27-28)
    - Mathematics, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 29-30)
    - Medieval Studies, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 31-32)
    - Molecular Biophysics Biochemistry, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 33-34)
    - Molecular, Cellular Developmental Biology, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 35-36)
    - Music, Dept of, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 37-38)
    - Near Eastern Languages Civilizations, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 39-40)
    - Neurobiology, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 41-42)
    - Neuroscience, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 43-44)
    - Pathology, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 45)
    - Pharmacology, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 46-47)
    - Philosophy, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 48-49)
    - Physics, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 50-51)
    - Political Science, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 52-53)
    - Psychology, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 54-55)
    - Religious Studies, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 56-57)
    - Russian and East European Studies, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 58-59)
    - Slavic Languages Literatures, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 60-61)
    - Sociology, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 62-63)
    - Spanish and Portuguese, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 64-65)
    - Statistics, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 66-67)
    - Theatre Studies, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 68)
    - Professional Schools
      - Architecture, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 69)
      - Art, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 70)
      - Divinity School, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 71-72)
      - Drama School, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 73)
      - Law School, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 74-75)
      - Management, School of, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 76-77)
      - Medical School, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 78-79)
      - Music, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 80)
      - Nursing, 1998-1999 (Box 12, Folder 81)
    - Yale College-Exchange Scholars grades, 1999-2000 (Box 12, Folder 82)
    - African American Studies, 1999-2000 (Box 12, Folder 83-84)
    - African Studies, 1999-2000 (Box 12, Folder 85-86)
    - American Studies, 1999-2000 (Box 12, Folder 87-88)
    - Anthropology, 1999-2000 (Box 12, Folder 89-90)
    - Applied Physics, 1999-2000 (Box 12, Folder 91)
    - Archaeology, 1999-2000 (Box 12, Folder 92)
    - Astronomy, 1999-2000 (Box 12, Folder 93-94)
    - Cell Biology, 1999-2000 (Box 12, Folder 95-96)
    - Cellular Molecular Physiology, 1999-2000 (Box 12, Folder 97-98)
    - Chemistry, 1999-2000 (Box 12, Folder 99-100)
    - Chemical Engineering, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Classics, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 2-3)
    - Combined BBS, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Comparative Literature, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 5-6)
    - Computer Science, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 7-8)
    - East Asian Languages Literatures, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 9-10)
    - East Asian Studies, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 11-12)
    - Ecology Evolutionary Biology, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 13-14)
    - Economics, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 15-16)
    - Engineering Applied Science, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 17-18)
    - Electrical Engineering, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - English, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 20-21)
    - Epidemiology Public Health, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 22-23)
    - Experimental Pathology, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 24-25)
    - Forestry and Environmental Studies, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 26-27)
    - French, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 28-29)
    - Genetics, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 30-31)
    - Geology Geophysics, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 32-33)
    - Germanic Languages Literatures, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 34-35)
    - History, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 36-37)
    - History of Art, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 38-39)
    - History of Science, History of Medicine, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 40-41)
    - Immunobiology, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 42-43)
    - International Development Economics, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 44-45)
    - International Relations, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 46-47)
    - Italian Language Literature, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 48-49)
    - Linguistics, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 50-51)
    - Management, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 52-53)
    - Mathematics, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 54-55)
    - MD/PhD, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 56)
    - Medieval Studies, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 57-58)
    - Microbiology, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 59-60)
    - Molecular Biophysics Biochemistry, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 61-62)
    - Molecular, Cellular Developmental Biology, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 63-64)
    - Music, Dept of, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 65-66)
    - Near Eastern Languages Civilizations, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 67-68)
    - Neurobiology, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 69)
    - Neuroscience, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 70-71)
    - Pharmacology, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 72-73)
    - Philosophy, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 74-75)
    - Physics, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 76-77)
    - Political Science, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 78-79)
    - Psychology, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 80-81)
    - Religious Studies, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 82-83)
    - Russian and East European Studies, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 84-85)
    - Slavic Languages Literatures, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 86-87)
    - Sociology, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 88-89)
    - Spanish and Portuguese, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 90-91)
    - Statistics, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 92-93)
    - Professional Schools
      - Art, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 94)
      - Divinity School, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 95-96)
      - Law School, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 97-98)
      - Management, School of, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 99-100)
      - Medical School, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 101)
      - Music, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 102)
      - Other Schools, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 103)
    - Yale College, 1999-2000 (Box 13, Folder 104)
    - African American Studies, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 1-2)
    - African Studies, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 3-4)
    - American Studies, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 5-6)
    - Anthropology, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 7-8)
    - Archaeology, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Astronomy, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 10-11)
    - Cell Biology, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 12-13)
    - Cellular Molecular Physiology, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 14-15)
    - Chemistry, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 16-17)
    - Classics, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 18-19)
    - Combined BBS, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 20)
    - Comparative Literature, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 21-22)
    - Computer Science, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 23-24)
    - East Asian Languages Literatures, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 25-26)
    - East Asian Studies, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 27-28)
    - Ecology Evolutionary Biology, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 29-30)
    - Economics, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 31-32)
    - Engineering Applied Science, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 33-34)
    - English, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 35-36)
    - Epidemiology Public Health, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 37-38)
    - Experimental Pathology, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 39-40)
    - Forestry and Environmental Studies, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 41-42)
    - French, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 43-44)
    - Genetics, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 45-46)
    - Geology Geophysics, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 47-48)
    - Germanic Languages Literatures, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 49-50)
    - History, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 51-52)
    - History of Art, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 53-54)
    - History of Science, History of Medicine, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 55-56)
    - Immunobiology, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 57-58)
    - International Relations, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 59-60)
    - Investigative Medicine, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 61-62)
    - Italian Language Literature, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 63-64)
    - Linguistics, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 65-66)
    - Management, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 67-68)
    - Mathematics, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 69-70)
    - Microbiology, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 71-72)
    - Molecular Biophysics Biochemistry, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 73-74)
    - Molecular, Cellular Developmental Biology, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 75-76)
    - Music, Dept of, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 77-78)
    - Near Eastern Languages Civilizations, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 79-80)
    - Neurobiology, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 81-82)
    - Neuroscience, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 83-84)
    - Pharmacology, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 85-86)
    - Philosophy, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 87-88)
    - Physics, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 89-90)
    - Political Science, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 91-92)
    - Psychology, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 93-94)
    - Religious Studies, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 95-96)
    - Russian and East European Studies, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 97-98)
    - Slavic Languages Literatures, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 99-100)
    - Sociology, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 101-102)
    - Spanish and Portuguese, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 103-104)
    - Statistics, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 105-106)
    - Theatre Studies, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 107)
    - Women's, Gender, and Sexuality Studies, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 108-109)
    - Professional Schools
      - Architecture, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 110-111)
      - Art, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 112)
      - Divinity School, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 113)
      - Law School, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 114)
      - Management, School of, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 115-116)
      - Nursing, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 117)
    - Teacher Prep, 2000-2001 (Box 14, Folder 118)
    - African American Studies, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 1-2)
    - African Studies, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 3-4)
    - American Studies, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 5-6)
    - Anthropology, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 7-8)
    - Archaeology, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 9-10)
    - Astronomy, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 11-12)
    - Cell Biology, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 13-14)
    - Cellular Molecular Physiology, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 15-16)
    - Chemistry, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 17-18)
    - Classics, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 19-20)
    - Comparative Literature, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 21-22)
    - Computer Science, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 23-24)
    - East Asian Languages Literatures, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 25-26)
    - East Asian Studies, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 27-28)
    - Ecology Evolutionary Biology, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 29-30)
    - Economics, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 31-32)
    - Engineering Applied Science, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 33-34)
    - English, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 35-36)
    - Epidemiology Public Health, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 37-38)
    - Experimental Pathology, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 39-40)
    - Forestry and Environmental Studies, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 41-42)
    - French, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 43-44)
    - Genetics, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 45-46)
    - Geology Geophysics, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 47-48)
    - Germanic Languages Literatures, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 49-50)
    - History, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 51-52)
    - History of Art, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 53-54)
    - History of Science, History of Medicine, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 55-56)
    - Humanities, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 57-58)
    - Immunobiology, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 59-60)
    - International Development Economics, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 61)
    - International Relations, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 62-63)
    - Investigative Medicine, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 64-65)
    - Italian Language Literature, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 66-67)
    - Judaic Studies, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 68)
    - Linguistics, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 69-70)
    - Management, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 71-72)
    - Mathematics, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 73-74)
    - Medieval Studies, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 75-76)
    - Microbiology, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 77-78)
    - Molecular Biophysics Biochemistry, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 79-80)
    - Molecular, Cellular Developmental Biology, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 81-82)
    - Music, Dept of, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 83-84)
    - Near Eastern Languages Civilizations, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 85-86)
    - Neurobiology, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 87-88)
    - Neuroscience, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 89-90)
    - Pharmacology, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 91-92)
    - Philosophy, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 93-94)
    - Physics, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 95-96)
    - Political Science, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 97-98)
    - Psychology, 2001-2002 (Box 15, Folder 99-100)
    - Religious Studies, 2001-2002 (Box 16, Folder 1-2)
    - Russian and East European Studies, 2001-2002 (Box 16, Folder 3-4)
    - Slavic Languages Literatures, 2001-2002 (Box 16, Folder 5-6)
    - Sociology, 2001-2002 (Box 16, Folder 7-8)
    - Spanish and Portuguese, 2001-2002 (Box 16, Folder 9-10)
    - Statistics, 2001-2002 (Box 16, Folder 11-12)
    - Professional Schools
      - Architecture, 2001-2002 (Box 16, Folder 13-14)
      - Drama School, 2001-2002 (Box 16, Folder 15-16)
      - Film Studies, 2001-2002 (Box 16, Folder 17-18)
      - Law School, 2001-2002 (Box 16, Folder 19-20)
      - Nursing, 2001-2002 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - African American Studies, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 22-23)
    - African Studies, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 24-25)
    - American Studies, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 26-27)
    - Anthropology, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 28-29)
    - Astronomy, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 30-31)
    - Cell Biology, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 32-33)
    - Cellular Molecular Physiology, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 34-35)
    - Chemistry, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 36-37)
    - Classics, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 38-39)
    - Comparative Literature, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 40-41)
    - Computer Science, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 42-43)
    - East Asian Languages Literatures, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 44-45)
    - East Asian Studies, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 46-47)
    - Ecology Evolutionary Biology, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 48-49)
    - Economics, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 50-51)
    - Engineering Applied Science, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 52-53)
    - English, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 54-55)
    - Epidemiology Public Health, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 56-57)
    - Experimental Pathology, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 58-59)
    - Forestry and Environmental Studies, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 60-61)
    - French, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 62-63)
    - Genetics, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 64-65)
    - Geology Geophysics, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 66-67)
    - Germanic Languages Literatures, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 68-69)
    - History, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 70-71)
    - History of Art, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 72-73)
    - History of Science, History of Medicine, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 74-75)
    - Immunobiology, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 76-77)
    - International Development Economics, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 78)
    - International Relations, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 79-80)
    - Investigative Medicine, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 81-82)
    - Italian Language Literature, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 83-84)
    - Linguistics, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 85-86)
    - Management, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 87-88)
    - Mathematics, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 89-90)
    - Medieval Studies, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 91)
    - Microbiology, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 92)
    - Molecular Biophysics Biochemistry, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 93-94)
    - Molecular, Cellular Developmental Biology, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 95-96)
    - Music, Dept of, 2002-2003 (Box 16, Folder 97-98)
    - Near Eastern Languages Civilizations, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 1-2)
    - Neurobiology, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Neuroscience, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 4-5)
    - Pharmacology, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 6-7)
    - Philosophy, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 8-9)
    - Physics, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 10-11)
    - Political Science, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 12-13)
    - Psychology, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 14-15)
    - Religious Studies, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 16-17)
    - Russian and East European Studies, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 18-19)
    - Slavic Languages Literatures, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 20-21)
    - Sociology, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 22-23)
    - Spanish and Portuguese, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 24-25)
    - Statistics, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 26-27)
    - Women's, Gender, and Sexuality Studies, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Professional Schools
      - Architecture, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 29)
      - Art, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 30-31)
      - Divinity School, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 32-33)
      - Drama School, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 34)
      - Law School, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 35-36)
      - Nursing, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 37)
    - Teacher Prep, 2002-2003 (Box 17, Folder 38-39)
    - Misc Grade Rosters A, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 40-42)
    - Administrative Sciences A Term, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - Administrative Sciences B Term, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Administrative Sciences Full Year, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - American Studies A Term, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - American Studies B Term, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - American Studies Full Year, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - Anatomy A Term, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - Anatomy B Term, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - Anatomy Full Year, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 51)
    - Anthropology A Term, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 52)
    - Anthropology B Term, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 53)
    - Anthropology Full Year, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 54)
    - Astronomy A Term, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 55)
    - Astronomy B Term, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 56)
    - Biology A Term, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 57)
    - Biology B Term, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 58)
    - Biology Full Year, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 59)
    - Forestry, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 60)
    - Summer Term, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 61)
    - Department of Education Courses Grades, 1921-1922 (Box 17, Folder 64)
    - Department of Education Courses Grades, 1922-1923 (Box 17, Folder 65)
    - Department of Education Courses Grades, 1924-1924 (Box 17, Folder 66)
    - Department of Education Courses Grades, 1924-1925 (Box 17, Folder 67)
  - Graduate School Student Files - Master, 1993-1994
  - Graduate School Student Files - Master, 1994-1995
  - Graduate School Student Files - Master, 1995-1996
  - Graduate School Student Files - Ph.D., 1993-1994
  - Graduate School Student Files - Ph.D., 1994-1995
  - Graduate School Student Files - Ph.D., 1995-1996
- Student records for Ph.D. recipients, 1994-2008; Accession 2017-A-004
  Restricted until January 1, 2084
- Student records, 1999-2008; Accession 2018-A-011
- Withdrawn student records, 1977-2014; Accession 2018-A-016
  Restricted until January 1, 2090
- Degree lists, grades and student records, 1968-2007; Accession 2019-A-0030
  Student records are restricted until 2083 as established by Yale Corporation regulations http://web.library.yale.edu/mssa/collections/research-use-of-yale-university-archives.